<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-4703386652643425/2732484991</string>
    <string name="application_id">ca-app-pub-4703386652643425~6231826592</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="app_name">Counterfeit Money Detector</string>
    <string name="btngopro">Remove Ads</string>
    <string name="btnstart">Start UV</string>
    <string name="btnstart2">Check Watermark</string>
    <string name="btnhelp">How to use</string>
    <string name="btnabout">About</string>
    <string name="btnexit">Exit</string>
    <string name="btnyes">Yes !</string>
    <string name="btnno">Sorry but no </string>
    <string name="boxrate">We would greatly appreciate it if you could Rate Us on the play store</string>
    <string name="txtpropaganda">Hi there, I´m Rodrigo the developer of this app. i just finished developing a new game would you like to try it ? It´s free !</string>
    <string name="propagandatitulo">My new Game!</string>
    <string name="propagandayes">Yeah sure !</string>
    <string name="propagandano">No, thanks.</string>
    <string name="boxhelp">Put a bill on the screen and you will se the watermarks and in the case of the uv light some colored marks. Make shure to be in a dark place if using the uv light</string>
    <string name="btnboxrate">Rate Us</string>
    <string name="btninfo">More info about counterfeit</string>
    <string name="btnboxclose">Close</string>
    <string name="boxhelptitle">Help</string>
    <string name="boxstarttitle">Attention!</string>
    <string name="boxabouttitle">About</string>
    <string name="boxabout">Conterfeit Money Detecotr was designed by Rodrigo Gonzalez Fantino. Did you like this app?</string>
    <string name="btnnext">Next</string>
    <string name="btnprevious">Previous</string>
    <string name="btnpa">Pesos Argentinos</string>
    <string name="txta">Anverso</string>
    <string name="txtr">Reverso</string>
    <string name="menuInitUV">Init UV</string>
    <string name="menucheckWatermark">Check watermarks</string>
    <string name="menuNoteSpec">Note specifications</string>
    <string name="menuHelp">Help</string>
    <string name="menuRemoveAdds">Remove adds</string>
    <string name="menuCredits">Credits</string>
    <string name="menuShare">Share</string>
    <string name="Currency"><b>Currency</b></string>
    <string name="country"><b>Country</b></string>
    <string name="Denomination">Denomination</string>
    <string name="securityMeasures"><b>Security Features</b></string>
    <string name="watermark"><b>Watermarks</b></string>

    <string name="real_50_watermark">Put the note near the light and verify in the clearer area an animal and the note value</string>
    <string name="real_50_description">50 and 100 reais notes have an holographic sash  which has the following effects: \n A) Note value number and the "REAIS" word \n B) The animal changes his colour. C) The leaf (in the 50\'s notes) and the coral (in 100\' notes) reveals differens colours when you move it.</string>
    <string name="real_100_watermark">Put the note near the light and verify in the clearer area an animal and the note value</string>
    <string name="real_100_description">50 and 100 reais notes have an holographic sash  which has the following effects: \n A) NOte value number and the "REAIS" word \n B) The animal changes his colour. C) The leaf (in the 50\'s notes) and the coral (in 100\' notes) reveals differens colours when you move it.</string>


    <string name="peso_col_10K_watermark">In both sides you can see a disc which turns from green to violet.</string>
    <string name="peso_col_10K_description">It has a metallic ink which becomes fluorescent green under ultroviolet light. Also you have a security transparent mark where you can read "BRC 10.000" when you see it against the light. Also has touch sensitive printing in the folowing areas: note denomination "Banco de la República" and in the picture</string>
    <string name="peso_col_50K_watermark">In both sides you cann see the Jorge Isaacs picture and a fragment from "Maria\'s" novel, when you see the note against the light </string>
    <string name="peso_col_50K_description">This note has 2 security threads. On the back you can see a dark band. And in the head you will see a thread in five silver segments, when you can see written "50 MIL PESOS COLOMBIA". Also you can read 50 MIL BRC near the down side of the picture. Finally, you should find some touch sensitive printing in some areas </string>

    <string name="share_text_dialog">I have just the Money Detector. Do you want to verify your notes? </string>
    <string name="andrioid_playstore_url">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.appsimple.DetectorBilleteFalso2</string>


    <string name="yuan_all_watermark">The most effective way to detect a fake Chinese money is the watermark. Hold the bill up against light, a watermark of Chairman Mao is shown. The watermark on a real 100 Yuan banknote is distinct while the watermark on a fake one is rather obscure.</string>
    <string name="yuan_all_description">The second way to detect a fake Chinese banknote is to scratch the hair of Chairman Mao. You can feel the hair on a real banknote. But on a fake banknote, the hair can not be felt.  \n  \n Another way to detect a fake bill is to see if there is 100, 50, 20 or 10 in the blue circle area when you pivot the banknote horizontally and slowly. </string>

    <string name="pmex_all_watermark">This is an image that is manufactured directly onto the cotton-paper and the polymer substrate and can be seen on both sides of the banknote when placed against the light, with all its details and different tones. \n  \n The watermark on the F type banknotes is an image of the bust-head figure of the note. In the case of the commemorative 200-peso banknote, it is the image of the Winged Victory.  The commemorative 100-peso banknote does not have this security element. \n  \n The 100-, 200-, the commemorative 200-, the 500- and 1000-peso banknotes have an additional watermark which is the image of the denomination number. \n  \n </string>
    <string name="pmex_all_description">This is an image that is manufactured directly onto the cotton-paper and the polymer substrate and can be seen on both sides of the banknote when placed against the light, with all its details and different tones.INTAGLIO AND EMBOSSING PERCEPTIBLE BY TOUCH \n Some features of the banknote’s surface are in raised print (intaglio and/or embossing), which is perceptible by touch, specially the “Banco de México” text, the bust-head figure, the denomination number, the mark for the blind and visually impaired people, and the denomination in letters. Cotton-paper banknotes have intaglio in the color-shifting element and polymer notes have embossing in the clear window. \n  \n In the 20-peso banknote, the intaglio can be felt on the scale of justice; in the 50-peso banknote, on the cannons frame; in the 100-peso banknote, in the seated men; in the 200-peso banknote, on the books, the window and the inkwell; in the 500-peso banknote, on the arum lilies, the paintbrushes and the woman; and in the 1000-peso banknote, on the church and on the bell. The commemorative 100- and 200-peso banknotes also have raised print on the commemorative legend and on the number “2010”. This feature also appears on the diminishing text, in both cotton-paper notes and in the new 50-peso banknote. \n  \n When the banknote is new or has been hardly used, the intaglio and embossing is felt more easily. \n  \n  \n  \n COLOR-SHIFTING ELEMENT \n It is an element that changes color when the banknote is moved or tilted. \n  \n 500-peso banknote \n  \n The color-shifting effect is on the right-hand side of the flower, on the upper left-hand corner of the banknote. This feature is in intaglio, which is perceptible by touch. \n  \n 1000-peso banknote \n  \n The color-shifting effect is on the chapel and on right-hand side tower. This feature is in intaglio which is perceptible by touch. \n  \n  \n  \n  \n 3D-THREAD \n This thread is manufactured directly onto the cotton-paper substrate. It has 3D figures in the form of snails. These figures move in opposite direction to how the banknote is shifted; if the banknote is moved to the sides, the figures move up and down; if the banknote is moved up and down, the figures shift to the sides. \n  \n The 3D-thread is red in the 100-peso banknote, green in the 200-peso banknote, brown in the 500-peso banknote, and violet in the 1000-peso banknote. \n  \n  \n MICROPRINTING \n The front and back microprinting texts which are very small texts, which usually require of a magnifying glass to be read. \n  \n 500-peso banknote \n  \n SE HA DICHO QUE LA REVOLUCIÓN NO NECESITA AL ARTE, PERO QUE EL ARTE NECESITA DE LA REVOLUCIÓN. ESO NO ES CIERTO. LA REVOLUCIÓN SÍ NECESITA UN ARTE REVOLUCIONARIO. \n DIEGO RIVERA. \n  \n 1000-peso banknote \n  \n "... SIN PATRIA NI LIBERTAD ESTAREMOS SIEMPRE A MUCHA DISTANCIA DE LA VERDADERA FELICIDAD" \n GRITO DE DOLORES \n 16 DE SEPTIEMBRE DE 1810 \n  \n  \n SECURITY THREAD \n  \n When holding the 100-, 200-, 500- and 1000-peso banknotes against the light, you can see a thread of approximately one millimeter (width) that crosses the note vertically. This thread is known as security thread and is manufactured directly onto the cotton-paper substrate. \n  \n This feature is detected when holding the banknote against the light. \n  \n  \n  \n FLUORESCENCE \n On the back of the banknotes there are designs printed with fluorescent ink, which glow when placed against ultraviolet light (also known as “black light”). The new 50-peso banknote has two fluorescent inks. \n  \n Fluorescencia en rev billetes F y F1 -inglés \n  \n Cotton paper banknotes they have color fibers on both sides—that is, tiny fibers embedded in the paper and distributed randomly. These fibers are fluorescent and can only be seen under black light. \n  \n In case of 100-, 200-, 500-, and 1000-peso banknotes, the 3D-thread also shines when a banknote is placed under a black light.</string>
    <string name="usd_100_watermark">Hold the note to light and look for a faint image of Benjamin Franklin in the blank space to the right of the portrait. The image is visible from both sides of the note.</string>
    <string name="usd_100_description">3D Security Ribbon \n Tilt the note back and forth while focusing on the blue ribbon. You will see the bells change to 100s as they move. When you tilt the note back and forth, the bells and 100s move side to side. If you tilt it side to side, they move up and down. The ribbon is woven into the paper, not printed on it. \n  \n  \n Color-Shifting Ink \n Tilt the note to see the Bell in the Inkwell and the numeral 100 in the lower right corner of the front of the note shift from copper to green. \n  \n Security Thread \n Hold the note to light to see an embedded thread running vertically to the left of the portrait. The thread is imprinted with the letters USA and the numeral 100 in an alternating pattern and is visible from both sides of the note. The thread glows pink when illuminated by ultraviolet light. \n  \n Raised Printing \n Move your finger up and down Benjamin Franklin’s shoulder on the left side of the note. It should feel rough to the touch, a result of the enhanced intaglio printing process used to create the image. Traditional raised printing can be felt throughout the $100 note, and gives genuine Federal Reserve notes their distinctive texture. \n  \n Microprinting \n Look carefully (magnification may be necessary) to see the small printed text THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA on Benjamin Franklin’s jacket collar, USA 100 around the blank space containing the portrait watermark, ONE HUNDRED USA along the golden quill, and small 100s in the note borders. \n </string>
    <string name="usd_50_watermark">Hold the note to light and look for a faint image of President Grant in the blank space to the right of the portrait. The image is visible from both sides of the note.</string>
    <string name="usd_50_description">Color-Shifting Ink \n Tilt the note to see the numeral 50 in the lower right corner on the front of the note shift from copper to green. \n  \n Security Thread \n Hold the note to light to see an embedded thread running vertically to the right of the portrait. The thread is imprinted with the text USA 50 and a small flag in an alternating pattern and is visible from both sides of the note. The thread glows yellow when illuminated by ultraviolet light. \n  \n Raised Printing \n Move your finger along the note’s surface to feel the raised printing, which gives genuine Federal Reserve notes their distinctive texture. \n  \n Microprinting \n Look carefully (magnification may be necessary) to see the small printed text FIFTY, USA, and 50 inside two of the blue stars to the left of the portrait, FIFTY repeated within both side borders of the note, and THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA In President Grant’s collar. \n  \n </string>

    <string name="peso_arg_50_description"> There are 2 kind of 50 pesos notes: one of "Faustino Sarmiento" and the other one has the Malvinas island. \n Both of them has optic ink, which colors depends on the angle of vision. The picture and other parts are raised painted. They will feel rough to the touch. Also you will finde a security thread running vertically to the left of the portrait (You can read BCRA and note value). 3d Security ribbon: if you tilt the note you will be able to see sarmiento\'s portrait and a albatross in the malvinas note.. Also this last note include blind marks</string>
    <string name="peso_arg_50_watermark"> In sarmiento\'s notes you can find a dark tiny sash which says "BCRA" and the denomination . In the other one, the watermark has the malvinas islands and their initial: IM  </string>

    <string name="peso_arg_100_description"> You will find 2 kind of notes: the old ones about Argentino Roca, and the new ones which Eva Peron.  \n In the first one, the 100 number at the top left corner has color shifting ink. The portrait is touch sensitive, and has in its left a security thread  in which you can read "BCRA" and note denomination. The eva peron one, has the following aditional security features:\n  A) In top/left corder you will find a trasparent weighing scale. \n B) Color shifting ink which changes his color progressively. Both notes have blind marks </string>
    <string name="peso_arg_100_watermark">For Argentino\'s Roca notes, the watermark has his portrait and initials: (J.A.R). In the Eva Peron one, you will find her portrait and initial (E.D.P.) </string>
    <string name="denomination_generic"> All</string>
    <string name="eur_all_watermark">Look at the banknote against the light. A faint image and the value become visible. If, however, you put the banknote on a dark surface, the watermark becomes darker.</string>
    <string name="eur_all_description">Paper \n Feel the banknote. It should be crisp and firm. \n  \n Raised print \n Run your finger across the front of the banknote. The ink is thicker in some parts. \n  \n Security thread \n Look at the banknote against the light. The security thread – a dark line running through the banknote – becomes visible. The word “EURO” and the value can be seen in tiny letters in the thread. \n  \n See-through number \n Look at the banknote against the light. The marks printed in the top-left corner on the front and the top-right corner on the back of the banknote combine perfectly to form the value. \n  \n Hologram \n When you tilt the banknote, the hologram shows the value of the note and a window or doorway. \n  \n Colour-changing number \n Tilt the banknote. On the back, the number changes colour from purple to olive green or brown. \n  \n  Microprint \n On some areas of the banknote you can see tiny writing. This microprint appears as a thin line to the naked eye, but can be read with a magnifying glass. Despite its small size, the print is sharp, not blurred. \n  \n Infrared properties \n When you look at the front of the banknote with an infrared device, only the right side of the main image remains visible. \n  \n UV properties \n Under ultraviolet light, the paper itself does not glow. Red, blue and green-coloured fibres embedded in the paper appear, the flag of the European Union looks green and the stars turn orange. The signature of the ECB’s President turns green. The large stars and small circles in the centre glow orange. On the back, the map, bridge and value appear in yellow. \n  </string>
    <string name="currency"><b>currency</b></string>


</resources>